<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Cats on</title><link>https://je-apartment.info/docs/cats/</link><description>Recent content in Cats on</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><lastBuildDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 08:48:23 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://je-apartment.info/docs/cats/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>door blocks</title><link>https://je-apartment.info/docs/cats/doorblocks/</link><pubDate>Sat, 04 Mar 2023 12:49:06 -0600</pubDate><guid>https://je-apartment.info/docs/cats/doorblocks/</guid><description>why? #
scout likes to accidently lock himself in the bedrooms. so we&amp;rsquo;re going to block the doors. you can move them while you are here, or even if you are leaving for a while, but re-block them before you leave at the end of your stay.</description></item><item><title>emergecy</title><link>https://je-apartment.info/docs/cats/emergency/</link><pubDate>Sat, 04 Mar 2023 12:49:06 -0600</pubDate><guid>https://je-apartment.info/docs/cats/emergency/</guid><description>vet #
Woodlake Vet Hospital 6436 Lyndale Ave S woodlakeveterinaryhospital.com
theres some fold-up cat carriers in erics closet, kinda burried behind some things.
if you need to go to the vet for some reason, the cats will throw up. take the jeep. keys are in a drawer on the right side of the island.
rocket #
rocket throws up food once every 2 or 3 months. if he does, just pick up with a paper towel and throw away.</description></item><item><title>food and water</title><link>https://je-apartment.info/docs/cats/food-and-water/</link><pubDate>Sat, 04 Mar 2023 12:49:06 -0600</pubDate><guid>https://je-apartment.info/docs/cats/food-and-water/</guid><description>bowls #
we&amp;rsquo;ll leave two food bowls and two water bowls. make sure to fill both sets of bowls before you leave. when you arrive, empty and fill water bowls.
food #
food is in the bin in the front closet next to the litter box. you can fill their food anytime.
water #
they like fresh water but they&amp;rsquo;ll be fine. they like an ice-cube or two in the water as well.</description></item><item><title>litterbox</title><link>https://je-apartment.info/docs/cats/litterbox/</link><pubDate>Sat, 04 Mar 2023 12:49:06 -0600</pubDate><guid>https://je-apartment.info/docs/cats/litterbox/</guid><description>changing the bag #
pull the bottom drawer out
take bag out
put a new bag in
top off the globe part with a little bit of litter
there is a max-fill line on the liner press the reset button
throw the bag away
vacuum if theres a lot of liter built up. vacuum is in the coat closet across from the island.
if the lights are flashing blue #
change the bag, even if it doesn&amp;rsquo;t seem super full.</description></item><item><title>toys</title><link>https://je-apartment.info/docs/cats/toys/</link><pubDate>Sat, 04 Mar 2023 12:49:06 -0600</pubDate><guid>https://je-apartment.info/docs/cats/toys/</guid><description>lost toys #
sometimes the cats play too hard and their toys go under the couch. if they seem extra bored or pent up you can use the broom stick thing thats partially under the couch to try and fish them out. the cats will appreciate you.</description></item></channel></rss>